[Music]
[音乐]
all right that start is thank you for
好的开始就是谢谢你
being here it's a full room it's a real
在这里，这是一个完整的房间，是一个真正的
project that we're presenting here today
今天在这里介绍的项目
so we really hope you enjoy it yeah it's
所以我们真的希望您喜欢它
the real stuff now and we are proud to
真正的东西，我们为此感到自豪
show you what we've been doing in the
向您展示我们在
past almost three years with Kafka in
在卡夫卡工作了近三年
the investment segment it's a stock
投资部分是股票
market trading and and we're going to
市场交易，我们将
show you a little bit about it I'm
给你看一点我
Marcos my I'm from Brazil but I've been
Marcos我来自巴西，但我一直
living in Amsterdam for around four four
在阿姆斯特丹住了大约四四个
years more or less it's a great place to
或多或少是一个很棒的地方
be ing ing is very innovative Bank my
拥有非常创新的银行
background is in distributed computing I
背景是分布式计算
worked with applications ever since
从那时起就与应用程序合作
before mm a lot of message-oriented
在mm之前很多面向消息的
middleware in my career mostly big
我职业中的中间件很大
customers I worked for now no existing
我现在工作的客户不存在
companies like ba and Borland that if do
像ba和Borland这样的公司
you know them that jbuilder before you
你知道他们在你之前的jbuilder
use IntelliJ was amazing too in WebLogic
在WebLogic中使用IntelliJ也很棒
server that was acquired by by Oracle
被Oracle收购的服务器
later I also worked in worldwide tamina
后来我也在世界各地的田鼠工作
with IBM for WebSphere for many years so
与IBM for WebSphere合作多年
I really worked with really huge
我真的和巨大的人一起工作
customers on the finance sector for for
金融行业的客户
a long time and yeah I'm working a tune
很久了，是的，我正在努力
of years for ing Dow I'm interested in
我感兴趣的陶氏公司
event-driven architectures using spring
使用Spring的事件驱动架构
since the early days occasional speaker
自从早期偶尔说话
conferences and meetups and yeah we did
会议和聚会，是的，我们做了
a quite interesting project on Kafka and
关于Kafka的一个非常有趣的项目，
it's really happy to share that
很高兴分享
knowledge today with you guys so to
今天与你们一起了解
continue live a bit about ing ing is the
继续生活一下ing是
most innovative Bank probably one of the
最创新的银行可能是
most innovative banks in the world it's
世界上最创新的银行
a bit different than any bank that you
与您的任何一家银行都有一点不同
might have worked or known before it's
可能早已奏效或知道
really pushing to be an IT company for
真正推动成为一家IT公司
many years now so it's really doing
很多年了，所以它真的在做
cutting-edge technology trying to
尖端技术试图
flatten the structures and building a
展平结构并建造一个
career a technical career path for
职业生涯的技术职业道路
developers it's really pushing in that
开发人员真的在推动
direction it's present in over 40
方向超过40
countries there is over 15
有超过15个国家
vacancies open so if you are interested
空缺职位，所以如果您有兴趣
you can take a look at it over 20
你可以看看它超过20
different countries so it's quite
不同的国家，这是相当
interesting and yeah let's start a
有趣，是的，让我们开始
little bit about our agenda today then
那么今天我们的议程
so we are going to explain a little bit
所以我们要解释一下
about our use case why we start this
关于我们的用例，为什么我们开始这个
project in first case in in the first
在第一个案例中第一个案例
place about Miffy to basically was the
关于米菲的地方基本上是
kickstart for us we're going to show you
为我们揭开序幕，我们将向您展示
a bit about our mobile investments
关于我们的移动投资
application over our architecture by the
在我们架构上的应用
way everything we are showing here as I
就像我们在这里展示的一切一样
mentioned it's real thing it's in
提到它是真实的东西
production it's it's working some of the
生产，这是一些工作
code of its not but we're going to get
它的代码，但我们将得到
there we're going to do a demo we're
在那里我们要做一个演示
going to talk about matrix in monitoring
谈谈监控矩阵
which is extremely important for us
这对我们来说非常重要
Kafka streams local development how we
卡夫卡促进了当地发展
do it lessons learned and we're going to
吸取教训，我们将
be open for a few questions hopefully if
希望开放一些问题，如果
you have time exactly
你有时间
yeah so just a quick disclaimer before
是的，所以之前只是一个快速免责声明
we start because with e9g we have a lot
我们开始，因为有了e9g，我们有很多
of regulations we have security
有安全性的法规
measurements so we could not actually
测量，所以我们实际上无法
show you the real production code today
向您展示真实的生产代码
but yeah we wouldn't come up here on the
但是是的，我们不会在这里
stage just solely showing your slides so
舞台只显示幻灯片
we really would like to show you real
我们真的想向您展示真实
code so we created basically sort as a
代码，因此我们基本上将其创建为
pet project but grew out to some kind of
宠物项目，但后来发展为某种
really nice lab projects that yeah works
是的，非常好的实验室项目
for us and that's actually what we're
对我们来说，这实际上就是我们
going to show you today but it's
今天要告诉你，但是
inspired on the work we did within ing
启发了我们所做的工作
and then yeah we will promise you it's
然后，是的，我们将向您保证
at least as interesting as the real
至少和真实的一样有趣
project maybe if you're better because
项目，也许你会更好，因为
if you do things for the second time
如果你第二次做事
you always make better decisions so
你总是做出更好的决定，所以
we're really happy to share that
我们很高兴分享
knowledge with you today
今天和你在一起
yeah before we continue the investment
是的，在我们继续投资之前
domain is quite a complex domain so we
域是一个非常复杂的域，所以我们
will like to keep our business lingo as
希望保持我们的业务术语
limited as possible but if you heard a
尽可能限制，但如果您听到
name or the term tick please remember
名称或术语打勾请记住
this slide then we talk about a price
这张幻灯片，然后我们讨论价格
update on a stock so we are in the
更新股票，所以我们在
investments Department of Energy
能源投资部
yeah where it all started it started
是的，一切从哪里开始
with a with the regulation and it sounds
与法规，这听起来
might really boring but for us it was
可能真的很无聊，但对我们来说
really a nice journey to get started
真的是一个不错的入门旅程
with with Kafka so the European
与卡夫卡在一起，所以欧洲
Parliament came up with this regulation
国会提出了这项规定
after the financial crisis - yeah
金融危机之后-是的
actually protect the customers in the
真正保护客户
end yeah to avoid losing a lot of money
是的，避免损失很多钱
on investments and just emphasize not
关于投资，只是不强调
only ING had to implement this
只有ING必须实施
regulation all European banks had to do
所有欧洲银行必须做的监管
this and yeah the actual regulation is
这是的，实际的规定是
quite a big book right we only show you
相当大的书吧，我们只告诉你
a really small part of deaths today and
今天死亡的一小部分
actually the most interesting part that
其实最有趣的部分
worked for us so basically our
为我们工作，所以基本上
requirement was is literally the the
要求实际上是
title of this slide inform our
这张幻灯片的标题告知我们
investment customers when they stock
存货时投资客户
drops in price ten percent at the end of
价格在年底下降百分之十
the day so we sent them out an SMS or a
那天，所以我们给他们发了短信或
push notification in the app but yeah at
在应用程序中推送通知，但在
the end of the day you probably lost a
一天结束时，您可能会失去
rally already quite a lot of money right
集会已经有很多钱了
so we sit down with our product owners
所以我们和产品负责人坐下来
with people from the basis and we said
与基础的人一起，我们说
okay this is the requirement from the
好吧，这是来自
regulation but we can do better right we
监管，但我们可以做得更好
should do this in real time because then
应该实时执行此操作，因为
our customers can connect accordingly
我们的客户可以进行相应的连接
and hopefully save some money so that's
并希望节省一些钱，所以
where we where we started to give you a
我们从哪里开始给您一个
bit of context I would like to show you
我想告诉你一些背景
some some screens of our mobile
我们手机的一些屏幕
investment app that our customers using
客户使用的投资应用程序
a lot of course we also have a web
当然，我们也有一个网站
facing interface but we see more and
面向界面，但我们看到了更多
more people are using the mobile
越来越多的人在使用手机
application so let's consider your fa
应用程序，所以让我们考虑一下你的fa
investment account within ING yes a lot
ING内的投资账户很多
of stocks in your portfolio and you can
您投资组合中的股票数量，您可以
you can see your stocks and you would
你可以看到你的股票，你会
like to set a an alert on on one of your
想对您的其中一个设置警报
stocks in your portfolio so you can you
投资组合中的股票，以便您可以
can see those alerts that you're going
可以看到您要去的那些警报
to create you can create alerts you can
创建您可以创建警报，您可以
delete them and never know
删除它们，永远不知道
you of them that's pretty
他们中的你很漂亮
straightforward so next to the required
简单明了，所以旁边是必需的
10% drop in price yeah the business also
价格下降10％是的
came up with and nice ideas so we took
想出了好主意，所以我们采取了
it quite positive approach to on top of
这是非常积极的方法
the head the regulation also basically
头规也基本上
features for the customer because yeah
为客户提供的功能，因为
if the price goes up you might want to
如果价格上涨，您可能想要
sell it because you can actually make
出售它，因为您实际上可以
some money and then they ask us oh can
一些钱，然后他们问我们哦可以
you also do this on a specific price or
您也可以按特定价格执行此操作，或者
not only on a percentage but don't also
不仅有一定百分比，而且没有
on a specific price so for example if
以特定的价格，例如
the ing stock reaches the price of let's
存货达到了我们的价格
say 12 euros I would like to get a
说12欧元，我想得到
notification so I can do something with
通知，以便我可以做一些事情
that in the customer can not only create
在客户中不仅可以创造
one notifications but can basically set
一个通知，但基本上可以设置
multiple notifications so yeah they get
多个通知，所以他们得到了
notified and it's a bit annoying right
通知，这有点烦人了
if you create an alert and you have to
如果创建警报，则必须
log in again when it is matched and so
匹配时再次登录，如此
they also ask us are ok you create
他们还问我们好吗，您创建
recurring alerts so customers don't have
定期提醒，使客户没有
to log in and create those by hand so
登录并手动创建
along the way a lot of requirements came
一路走来，有很多要求
in and step by step the project became a
在逐步的项目成为
bit more complex and then the most
有点复杂，然后最
tricky thing came at that time that we
当时棘手的事情来了
start implementing because they say yeah
开始实施，因为他们说是的
realize if you would like to do this
意识到如果你想这样做
real time we are dealing with a constant
实时我们正在处理一个常数
stream of price updates sticks from the
价格更新流从
market and that can go up between 2000
市场，并且可以在2000年之间上升
up to 12,000 a second
每秒高达12,000
especially as Trump is tweeting around
特别是在特朗普发推文时
and we see it say hey it can't go crazy
我们看到它说嘿，它不会发疯
right so we have to be prepared for that
对，所以我们必须为此做好准备
so yeah where did we start yeah we
所以是的，我们从哪里开始的，是的，我们
didn't initially thought about Kafka in
最初并没有想到过卡夫卡
the beginning we had a lot of fuss about
一开始我们大惊小怪
it it was happening and trending but we
它正在发生和趋势，但我们
first yeah did a lot of pocs we tried to
首先，我们尝试了很多pocs
store data in elasticsearch we played
将数据存储在我们玩过的elasticsearch中
around with spring batch but in the end
到Spring Batch处理，但最后
we quickly realized that that we needed
我们很快意识到我们需要
some kind of streaming platform to deal
某种流媒体平台来处理
with this huge amount of data coming in
大量的数据进入
and on the order and matching this
并在订单上与之匹配
against the thousands of alerts
针对成千上万的警报
by our customers and we we cannot stop
受客户欢迎，我们无法停止
this it's yeah we would like to do this
是的，我们要这样做
real time so that's where our journey
实时，这就是我们的旅程
begin on our team we had a really
开始我们的团队，我们有一个非常
experienced spring knowledge spring
有经验的Spring 知识Spring
booth and we found out that within ing
摊位，我们发现
there was a team managing a cutter
有一个团队管理刀具
cluster already for years so they were
已经集群好几年了
really mature in in managing this Khafre
在管理这个Khafre方面真的很成熟
Christopher for us it was really
克里斯托弗对我们来说真的
convenient because we didn't have to
方便，因为我们不必
worry about disk Africa list we didn't
担心磁盘非洲列表，我们没有
have to manage ourselves so that's
必须管理自己，所以
actually where our our journey started
实际上是我们旅程的起点
before we going to show you some code
在我们向您展示一些代码之前
some live demos I would like to quickly
我想快速进行一些现场演示
show you how our yeah how our over
告诉你我们是怎么过的
architecture looks like to get some
建筑看起来像一些
pictures because you will see some of
图片，因为您会看到一些
the applications running so let's maybe
应用程序正在运行，所以让我们也许
start with with our end result we would
从我们的最终结果开始，我们将
like to send out the notification as
喜欢发送通知为
soon as possible to our customers and to
尽快给我们的客户和
do that first the customer needs to
客户首先需要这样做
create an alert and of course we create
创建警报，当然我们创建
alerts when they buy stocks with the
当他们购买股票时发出警报
application the web application and
应用Web应用程序和
they're also advisers that can on behalf
他们也是可以代表的顾问
of the customer great alerts because we
客户的重大警报，因为我们
still have also people calling on call
还有人在打电话
centers get advice so also the advisors
中心获得建议，顾问也获得建议
should be able to create alerts on the
应该能够在
office customer so that's basically
办公室客户，所以基本上
where it starts so we have a spring boot
它从哪里开始，所以我们有一个 spring boot
two application that's basically
基本上是两个应用
primarily offering a rest interface and
主要提供休息界面和
in the end store the alerts for the
最后存储警报
customer in the database that's pretty
漂亮的数据库中的客户
straightforward then we have another
简单，然后我们有另一个
components and that that component is
组件，该组件是
basically responsible for receiving
基本上负责接收
those price updates from the market and
这些来自市场的价格更新，
this one is going to push the constant
这将推动不断
stream of ticks on Kafka so far so good
到目前为止，Kafka的滴答声非常好
I mean reduce it to Kafka's pretty easy
我的意思是将其减少到Kafka相当容易
so that's what what worked fine to run a
所以这就是运行
Kafka you need the zookeeper and we also
卡夫卡，你需要 Zookeeper ，我们也
use the schema registry we will go into
使用架构注册表，我们将进入
that later on but for now this was
后来，但现在这是
managed for us so that was pretty pretty
为我们管理，所以这很漂亮
much
许多
then the heavy-lifting comes in because
然后重担来了，因为
now we have to mismatch this incoming
现在我们必须不匹配此传入
stream of tix against the number of
tix流对数量的影响
ticks and number of alerts in the
刻度线和警报数量
database but we cannot go 12 thousand
数据库，但我们不能去12000
times a second to the database because
每秒访问数据库一次，因为
that will not scale but this component
那不会扩展，但是这个组件
is basically responsible for matching it
基本上负责匹配它
matching the alerts and if there is a
匹配警报，如果有
match for one or maybe multiple
匹配一个或多个
customers it will push another offense
客户，它将推动另一种违法行为
basically on Kafka so there are no API
基本上是在Kafka上，所以没有API
calls between those applications so if
这些应用程序之间的调用，所以如果
and riffin and that notification surface
和riffin以及通知面板
is going to reach out to either a SMS
可以联系任何一条短信
gateway slash platform or a push
网关斜线平台或推送
platform to in the end deliver the
平台最终交付
notification be alert to the customer so
通知提醒客户，因此
this is in a high level actually what we
这实际上是在高层次上
what we built and we're going to run
我们建造了什么，我们将要运行
this whole thing locally so let's pray
这整个事情都是本地的，让我们祈祷
the demo gods everything will work fine
演示神一切正常
so let's switch to IntelliJ while team
所以我们在团队中切换到IntelliJ
is preparing to run it everything it's
正在准备运行它的一切
important to understand that the 12,000
重要的是要知道12,000
ticks per second for Kafka it's
卡夫卡每秒
basically very lightweight if you think
如果您认为基本上很轻巧
Kafka was developed to process really
Kafka被开发来真正处理
huge amounts of data but our biggest
大量的数据，但我们最大的
challenge there is not only those 12,000
挑战不只是那些12,000
ticks it's about matching 12,000 ticks
滴答声大约匹配12,000个滴答声
per second all the time because you see
一直保持每秒，因为您看到了
we trade from stock exchanges from all
我们从所有人的证券交易所进行交易
over the world so it's at its all the
遍及整个世界
time running and we have thousands of
运行时间，我们有成千上万
alerts creates per customers and you
警报会根据客户和您创建
cannot be behind because if you start to
不能落后，因为如果你开始
get behind a few seconds soon you're
很快落后几秒钟
very behind because we're processing a
非常落后，因为我们正在处理
lot so at the same time that we're
很多，所以同时我们
processing those alerts you have to
处理那些您必须
match against the existing alerts in and
与现有的警报匹配
keep moving forward you cannot stop
继续前进，你无法停止
because that's all this real-time for
因为所有这些都是实时的
instance when it's 3:00 in the afternoon
实例是下午3:00
the new york stock exchange in amsterdam
阿姆斯特丹纽约证券交易所
the new york stock exchange up in the US
美国的纽约证券交易所
and i mean it's it's an ongoing thing
我的意思是这是一个正在进行的事情
and that's one of the biggest challenge
这是最大的挑战之一
we have and also all the important
我们有，还有所有重要的
factor while everything is starting over
一切都开始的时候
there tim is going to explain to a nice
蒂姆要解释一个很好的
theme about this is
关于这个的主题是
Kafka fits very well with spring boot
Kafka非常适合 spring boot
model because you have control
模型，因为您有控制权
of your application instance and you
您的应用程序实例
have like you can scale multiple
就像你可以扩展多个
applications in Kafka delegates this
Kafka中的应用程序将其委托
scalability basically if you have the
基本上，如果您具有
proper number of partitions and etc to
适当数量的分区等
the client side so you can have control
客户端，以便您可以控制
over how low is outer scale in downscale
关于缩小的外部尺度有多低
your applications it's really a very
您的应用程序真的非常
good match because if you compare cup go
很好的匹配，因为如果您比较杯
with JMS and the old way of doing it it
使用JMS及其旧方法
really gives you it really gives you
真的给你它真的给你
this perfect model where you can manage
您可以管理的完美模型
and and prepare your application for
并准备您的申请
different payloads during the whole day
全天不同的有效载荷
so it really fits very well if you think
所以真的很适合
about it let's see there's one specific
关于它，让我们看看有一个特定的
thing about this demo we don't go in
这个演示的事情，我们不参加
deeper details about craft itself I hope
我希望对手工艺本身有更深入的了解
everyone I believe all of you have some
我相信你们所有人都有
understanding of Kafka and but it will
对卡夫卡的了解，但它将
be like a demo on top of it we're going
像一个演示一样，我们要
to talk about streams and about how we
谈论溪流以及我们如何
do joins and how we manage all these
参加以及我们如何管理所有这些
data more details and show a lot of code
记录更多详细信息并显示大量代码
yeah so what I actually did I started to
是的，所以我实际上开始
our set of talking posh files it started
我们开始谈论的豪华文件
Kafka it started tsuki / it started
Kafka开始tsuki /开始
Prometheus for our metrics markers going
普罗米修斯为我们的指标标记
to show that later on what else the
稍后再说明
database of course Postgres in this case
在这种情况下当然是Postgres的数据库
and we'd authorized all our spring good
并授权我们所有的 Spring 好
applications to basically start this
应用程序从根本上开始
thing okay everything is healthy so far
没关系，到目前为止一切都很健康
so good so in the next demo we're going
很好，所以在下一个演示中，我们将
to create a lot of ticks price updates
创建大量的价格变动
on stocks just to mimic the market
在股票上模仿市场
because we are not connected to a real
因为我们没有连接到真实的
stock market yeah party provider here
股票市场是这里的聚会提供者
so we basically mimic this but just for
所以我们基本上是模仿
this demo I don't want to do this
这个演示我不想这样做
because I would like to show you the
因为我想告诉你
flow through this applications and do
流经此应用程序并执行
these topics so what we're actually
这些主题，所以我们实际上是
going to do now is to mimic a customer
现在要做的是模仿客户
just free for you to know showing you on
只是免费让您知道向您展示
a mobile phone is a bit strange right so
手机有点奇怪，所以
for today the the notification the alert
对于今天的通知警报
will be delivered by mail so you cannot
将通过邮件发送，所以您不能
see it and just to to show
看到它只是为了展示
we're not tricking you the the inbox is
我们没有欺骗您，收件箱是
empty and let's let's see if it works
空，让我们看看它是否有效
fine and we are really really lazy back
很好，我们真的很懒
into fella purrs so for today our UI is
变成屁屁，所以今天我们的用户界面是
a swagger I hope you're all familiar
大摇大摆我希望你们都熟悉
with it so we're going to create an
用它，所以我们要创建一个
alert so today I'm custom one two three
警报，所以今天我自定义一二三
four five it's one of our most beloved
四五是我们最爱的人之一
customers and and let's yeah iPhone an
客户，让我们继续吧iPhone
Apple stock in my portfolio and we just
我的投资组合中有苹果股票，我们只是
looked up the price of an Apple stock
查找了苹果股票的价格
it's yeah it's going down actually a bit
是的，它实际上下降了一点
let's see so this is the actual price so
让我们看一下，这是实际价格，所以
let's copy this price and we're going to
让我们复制这个价格，我们将
create an alert in the system so this is
在系统中创建一个警报，所以这是
the base price should replace this way
基本价格应以此方式替换
the dots so it's almost 200 years and
点，所以差不多有200年了
yeah we all would like to get rich right
是的，我们都想致富
so if it reaches a price of $3,000 then
因此，如果价格达到$ 3,000，
I would like to get a notification let's
我想收到通知，让我们
see if that will happen each stock has a
看看是否会发生这种情况，每只股票都有一个
unique kind of symbol to identify a set
独特的符号来识别一套
of stock so the symbol here is a AAPL
库存，所以这里的符号是AAPL
right that's the Apple stock so let's
没错，那是苹果股票，所以让我们
create this alert in the system let's
在系统中创建此警报，让我们
see just to show you we're going to load
只是为了向您展示我们将要加载
all the alerts for this customer one two
该客户的所有警报一二
three four five and here we are we
三四五，我们在这里
created I don't know if it's visible in
创建了我不知道它是否在
the back and make it a bit bigger whew
背面，使其更大一点
we created this alert and if the stock
我们创建了此警报，如果库存
price reaches 3000 or of course higher
价格达到3000或更高
than 2000 we will have a match but now
比2000年我们将有一场比赛，但现在
we don't have ticks coming into the
我们没有滴答声进入
system and actually what we do locally
系统，实际上我们在本地做什么
we also don't want to connect to this
我们也不想连接到这个
third-party provider because we will be
第三方提供商，因为我们将
flooded with a lot of data right so most
充满了很多数据，所以最
of the time when we when we develop
当我们发展的时候
features we would like to be in control
我们希望控制的功能
of the ticks that we send so we created
我们发送的滴答声中创建的
our own kind of Kafka - so producers
我们自己的卡夫卡-生产者
really specific for our case so we can
确实针对我们的情况，所以我们可以
control
控制
the price of the stock at that moment
当时的股票价格
mimicking the stock market but it's only
模仿股市，但这仅仅是
one dick right just for this demo and
仅此演示就一个家伙
tada tada
多田多田
today it reaches the price a little bit
今天它达到了一点价格
over two thousand dollars it was a yeah
超过两千美元，是的
trade it on the nest and the nest egg
在巢和巢蛋上交易
exchange and this is the symbol so let's
交换，这是符号，所以让我们
let's run this coup sole producer it's
让我们来经营这个政变的唯一制片人
actually spring boot application it's
实际上是Spring Boot应用程序
not a web application it's just a
不是网络应用程序，它只是一个
command line runner that we can execute
我们可以执行的命令行运行程序
here and we basically say produce a
在这里，我们基本上说产生一个
stick on a Kafka topic for the Apple
坚持苹果的卡夫卡主题
stock and basically send out for this
库存，基本上为此发送
jesu file that will be converted into a
jesu文件将被转换为
fro later on but we will go there soon
以后再来，但是我们很快就会去
so
所以
let's execute this the comment line
让我们执行此注释行
renewal starts publish to take on Kafka
更新开始发布以采用Kafka
and now we should having a match right
现在我们应该有一场比赛
so let's let's take a look there we are
让我们来看看我们
the customer now received a notification
客户现在收到通知
on his phone in this case of course it's
在这种情况下，当然是在他的电话上
tml but just to show you the example
tml只是为了向您展示示例
right so everything was fine what
对，所以一切都很好
happens one of the hood quickly going to
发生其中之一的引擎盖很快
show you the Kafka topics we will go
向您展示我们将参加的卡夫卡主题
into depth later on but just quickly add
稍后再深入，只是快速添加
a few on the cluster maybe you can
集群上的一些也许
explain in the meantime what is - yeah
同时解释什么是-是的
this is the - originally developed by
这是-最初是由
Yahoo that it's important it's not there
雅虎重要的是不存在
anymore but it's quite simple to
了，但是它很简单
configure and because we start a few
配置，因为我们开始了一些
years ago probably you can there are
多年前可能你可以
very nice new tools actually but because
实际上是非常好的新工具，但是因为
we started many years ago this was one
我们是从很多年前开始的
of the best tools for us to run it
我们运行它的最佳工具
locally and basically to be able to keep
在本地，基本上可以保持
developing with Kafka and then we just
和卡夫卡一起发展，然后我们就
use it and it shows you were the broker
使用它，它表明您是经纪人
and the message is every topic the
消息是每个主题
partitions on the topics it's quite
在主题上划分很
interesting - and still available is
有趣-仍然可用
docker eyes so you can go to docker hub
码头工人的眼睛，所以你可以去码头工人中心
in download the image and just start
在下载图像并开始
using it and that's amazing for us yeah
使用它，这对我们来说是惊人的
and the really nice thing is that this
真正的好处是
is basically a few on top of your Kafka
基本上是您的Kafka上的一些
broker it can be multiple brokers but
经纪人可以是多个经纪人，但
you see that the Kafka topics where all
您会看到Kafka主题
the events and all the data is basically
事件和所有数据基本上是
flowing around it takes a little bit of
流动需要一点点
time to start seconds by the for it goes
是时候开始几秒钟了
to the broker and updates itself of
给经纪人并更新自己
course so it is a little bit should show
当然，它应该显示一点
there at some point and I have yeah on
在某个时候，我对
the last column here you can see exactly
您可以在这里的最后一列中看到
so we started off by creating this alert
所以我们首先创建此警报
so an offense will pop up on a on a
因此，进攻将会在
Kafka topic then the matcher picked it
卡夫卡主题，然后匹配者将其选中
up there was a match sent also an
上面有一场比赛也发送了
offense on another Kafka topic and in
在另一个Kafka主题上冒犯
the end our notification components sent
最后，我们的通知组件已发送
in this case the the alerts so there was
在这种情况下，警报，所以有
an event sent
已发送事件
in defense and what we did was we
在国防方面，我们所做的就是
basically put a roll tick on one of the
基本上对其中一个
kafka topics to to to basically
kafka主题到基本
kick-start this whole flow so this was
启动整个流程，所以这是
in the end the whole flow to the system
最终，整个系统流程
to all the topics and all the spring
所有主题和整个 Spring
good applications before we continue I
好的应用程序，然后我们继续
am NOT going to shut it down and we're
我不会关闭它，我们
going to start producing around five to
将开始生产约五到
eight thousand tics automatically and
八千个自动
we're also going to mimic customers
我们还将模仿客户
trading alerts in the system so we're
在系统中交易警报，因此我们
going to burn some CPU cycles here
这里会消耗一些CPU周期
through to mimic because this is one
通过模仿，因为这是一个
simple example so let's shut it down we
简单的例子，让我们关闭它
will go into the top compose file the
将进入最上面的撰写文件
whole setup played around but this was
整个设置都在玩，但这是
just a quick demo the key here it's the
只是一个快速演示，关键是
high performance of Kafka for us right
卡夫卡的高性能对我们来说是正确的
we need a high to put in character it's
我们需要很高的品格
very well-thought it's exactly for this
很好的想法就是为了这个
for this type of use cases the latest is
对于此类用例，最新的是
very low because it's used like zero
非常低，因为它被用作零
copy approach so it basically copy
复制方法，因此基本上可以复制
things directly from the buffer to the
东西直接从缓冲区到
network buffer and sends this over the
网络缓冲区，并通过
wire so it's extremely fast in this case
电线，因此在这种情况下非常快
we're running the whole set up in
我们正在运行整个设置
multiple docker instance that we also
我们也有多个docker实例
had a lot of experience with docker and
在docker上有很多经验
sprint booted so basically was a very
冲刺启动，所以基本上是一个非常
good fit for us and that's what we use
非常适合我们，这就是我们使用的
for development
为了发展
it really helps because locally you can
这确实有帮助，因为在本地您可以
basically simulate the whole system
基本模拟整个系统
which can be complex sometimes I think
我想有时候这可能很复杂
most of of you probably are using docker
你们大多数人可能正在使用docker
when you talk about this but let's go
当你谈论这个但我们走吧
back to the presentation a little bit ok
回到演示文稿还可以
so one of the key things for us of
所以对我们来说关键的事情之一
course it's about the matrix in
当然这是关于矩阵
monitoring so when we start this project
进行监控，以便我们启动该项目时
with it's ok we can have to write this
没关系，我们必须写这个
but we need insights and we start
但是我们需要洞察力，我们开始
looking around or what we're going to
环顾四周或我们要去
use and we saw micrometer and it's a
使用，我们看到了千分尺，这是一个
library that it's not beauty is
不是美丽的图书馆是
specifically for spring but it's a
专为 Spring 而设
pivotal project but it's built for
关键项目，但专为
agnostic you should be able to use it in
不可知论者，你应该能够在
any type of job applications but it fits
任何类型的工作申请，但都适合
really well spring boot it's basically
spring boot 真的很好，基本上
very well integrated and and it makes it
很好的集成，它使它
a bit easier if you using spring boot
如果您使用Spring Boot，会容易一些
like many other
像许多其他人一样
it's like a cell for J for matrix it's a
就像J的单元格是矩阵
manager basically everything yeah so one
经理基本上一切都是这样
of the key things for us is not is that
对我们来说关键的不是
with we we wanted more than only the
与我们一起，我们不仅想要
normal matrix do you have we want
正常矩阵你有我们想要的吗
business matrix on that because we need
业务矩阵，因为我们需要
to be keep an eye when we send another
当我们发送另一个时要注意
how long it's taking for actually for us
实际花了我们多长时间
to notify the customer and you also want
通知客户，您也想
to keep an eye on between the nodes how
密切关注节点之间的关系
it's the latest between days if you have
如果有的话，这是几天之间的最新时间
some bottleneck we want to immediately
我们要立即解决的一些瓶颈
know where the bottleneck is so we can
知道瓶颈在哪里，所以我们可以
scale that layer specifically of course
当然可以专门缩放该层
we can automate that as well but you
我们也可以自动化它，但是你
also want to visibility so you can prove
也想知道能见度，所以你可以证明
your algorithms between the flow and in
您在流程和流程之间的算法
things like that so this was really key
这样的事情，所以这真的很关键
for us and for you to understand a
让我们和您了解
little bit this part so let's imagine
一点这部分，让我们想象
this the stock exchange a bit about
这个股票交易所有关
matrix so the stock is traded so you do
矩阵，这样就可以交易股票了
a trade you buy stock this attic is
您买股票的交易，这个阁楼是
emitted we do an ingestion of this tick
发出了我们摄取此滴答声
that's what we call a row stock with a
这就是我们所说的带有
tick and we produce the stick to the
滴答作响，我们生产坚持
first Kafka topic so but when you think
第一个卡夫卡主题，所以当你想到
about this the raw data from the market
关于这一点，来自市场的原始数据
does not fit your internal systems so
不适合您的内部系统，因此
the first thing we need to do is to
我们要做的第一件事是
enrich that data with something that
通过一些丰富的数据
adds meaning that can be used by our
增加了我们可以使用的含义
internal system so we have out the
内部系统，所以我们有
business intelligence on top of it and
在其之上的商业智能和
that's the first step of it so what we
这是第一步，所以我们
do is we have a huge group of business
要做的是我们有大量的业务
experts that they keep all these stocks
专家，他们保留所有这些库存
we trade currently trade over 40,000
我们目前的交易量超过40,000
different kinds of instruments just for
各种不同的乐器
you to have an idea basically if we want
您基本上有一个想法，如果我们想要
to buy stock we have more than 40,000
买股票，我们有超过40,000
different options to buy what you want
购买您想要的东西的不同选择
and we have to match this because if we
我们必须匹配这个，因为如果我们
start to ingest this data in our systems
开始将这些数据吸收到我们的系统中
internally without these intelligence
内部没有这些情报
that they have no meaning for us so this
他们对我们没有意义，所以这
is the first step and what we do here
是第一步，我们在这里做什么
it's basic basically it's a Kafka stream
这基本上是卡夫卡流
in a K table I'm going to go in details
在K表中，我将详细介绍
about this and we do the join and we
关于这个，我们加入了，我们
produced to the second to the to the
生产到第二个到
third topic here where now all the data
这里的第三个话题现在所有数据
has a business meaning and we can it can
有商业意义，我们可以做到
be used by our internal systems
由我们的内部系统使用
to do that then of course we have a
为此，我们当然有一个
match engine and if there is a match
匹配引擎，如果有匹配项
there is a match we publish to another
我们发布了另一个比赛
topic and of course then there is a
主题，当然还有一个
notification service that we actually
我们实际上的通知服务
sent the information to our customers
发送信息给我们的客户
I'm gonna show a little bit about the
我将展示一些关于
monitory first can so let me show a
首先可以监视，让我展示一个
little bit how we did this monitoring I
一点点，我们如何做到这一点我
hope everything starts fine because in
希望一切都开始顺利，因为
this step what the team did is we
团队所做的这一步是我们
started the whole engine producing ticks
整个引擎开始运转
and we expect something at least 5000
我们期望至少有5000
ticks per second here - to show you how
每秒滴答声-向您展示
good copper can be to process this
好的铜可以加工
so yeah the system is fully health again
是的，系统再次完全健康
so I'm gonna do we sync our matrix to -
所以我要把矩阵同步到-
we use graph honor and with sync
我们使用图荣誉和同步
Romantics parameters in this example
本例中的Romantics参数
because it's fairly easy and that's what
因为这很容易，那就是
we're going to show so we have a graph
我们将展示，所以我们有一个图
on the board and it's important that you
在董事会上，重要的是您
keep in mind the picture I just showed
请记住我刚刚显示的图片
you with all the steps because that's
完成所有步骤，因为
basically what we should see around here
基本上我们应该在这里看到
so we have this board with matrix and it
所以我们有一块带有矩阵的板子
will take some time because when it was
将需要一些时间，因为
initializing the latest here is a bit
在这里初始化最新的有点
out but it's going to go up but here we
出来，但它会上升，但在这里我们
are now basically producing five
现在基本上生产五个
thousand and four hundred ticks per
每千四百s
second we are processing tests we also
第二，我们正在处理测试，我们也
have here a metric that you can see the
这里有一个指标，您可以看到
average size of every tick so this also
每个刻度的平均大小，所以这也
helps us and there are actually this is
帮助我们，实际上这是
the average size this is the current
当前的平均大小
bandwidth being used this also helps us
带宽的使用也对我们有帮助
to be prepared if we need more bandwidth
如果我们需要更多的带宽准备
bandwidth can be something important on
带宽可能是重要的
the stock market because when there is a
股市，因为当有
flourish of stocks you need your network
蓬勃发展的股票需要您的网络
to be prepared so we need to know that
要做好准备，所以我们需要知道
basically all the time so we can improve
基本上所有的时间，所以我们可以改善
there and do some work on them so this
在那里做一些工作，所以这
should be soon go away and then you see
应该很快就会消失，然后你看到
a more realistic graphic the initial
更加真实的图形
tick here took some time because it was
在这里打勾花了一些时间，因为
basically restarting we are generating
基本上重新启动我们正在生成
some alerts of course this is a smaller
一些警报，当然这是一个较小的
number because the load would be too too
数字，因为负载太大了
high but basically there are matches
高，但基本上有比赛
happening and alerts are being matched
发生并且警报正在匹配
and sent basically immediately and the
并基本上立即发送，
latest is extremely low so if we look
最新是非常低的，所以如果我们看
around here of course in a real
当然在这里周围
environment we have more or less
我们或多或少的环境
ten milliseconds Layton's between the
雷顿之间的十毫秒
application where there the server where
应用程序在哪里服务器在哪里
the application is running and the
该应用程序正在运行，并且
broker so you can just add ten
经纪人，所以你可以只加十
milliseconds in average per note but
每个音符的平均毫秒数，但
that's it that's basically the lateness
就是这样，基本上是晚了
we have in real life and here you can
我们有现实生活，在这里您可以
see more or less all these steps what
或多或少地看到所有这些步骤
happens so basically the first step is
发生，所以基本上第一步是
taking one millisecond because yeah we
花一毫秒是因为我们
generate the tick here and we process it
在此处生成刻度，我们对其进行处理
here but then we do the first step which
在这里，但是我们要做的第一步是
is that stream that we reach the data as
是我们到达数据的那个流
I explained to you guys and this is
我跟你们讲了
taking 50 milliseconds that it's the
花费50毫秒的时间
second topic so this is the joint
第二个话题，这是联合
happened then we do a match this is
发生了，然后我们进行一场比赛，这是
taking now 105 milliseconds and then we
现在花了105毫秒，然后我们
do we actually send the alert
我们实际上发送警报吗
so in this local environment the time
所以在这个当地环境下
between actually matching a generator
实际匹配发电机之间
and T doing the match and sending the
和T进行比赛并发送
alert it's about 180 80 milliseconds
提醒大约180 80毫秒
it's extremely efficient and the other
这是非常高效的，另一个
thing that's really important for us
对我们来说很重要的事情
it's about being scalable ing is in a
关于可扩展性
journey to became a global platform so
成为全球平台的旅程
what's happening now it's or building
现在正在发生什么或正在建造
your system or systems to now not not be
您的系统现在不是
more to not be localized anymore so we
更多不再本地化，所以我们
don't we don't want to have like a
难道我们不想拥有像
system for the Netherlands another
荷兰的另一个系统
system doing trading for the Belgium we
系统为比利时做交易
want a single system and the final goal
想要一个系统和最终目标
is to have the whole 40 countries using
是要让整个40个国家/地区使用
a single global platform to do this so
一个单一的全球平台可以做到这一点
the idea is that we really go more in
我们的想法是，
the direction of an IT company where you
您所在的IT公司的发展方向
have a center manage the per-unit that
有一个中心来管理每个单位
can handle basically the full workload
基本上可以处理全部工作量
worldwide and that's what we did join we
在全球范围内，这就是我们加入我们的过程
right now yeah so let me show some code
现在是的，所以让我显示一些代码
how this works this is extremely
这是怎么工作的
interesting because Kafka has some
有趣，因为卡夫卡有一些
features that really helps us to to do
真正帮助我们做的功能
this monitoring and I'll show you how
这个监控，我会告诉你如何
first thing
第一件事
Kafka the Catholic lines they expose one
卡夫卡天主教线他们暴露出一种
guy calls metrics reported this is a
家伙致电指标报告这是一个
calf internal and the matrix report
小牛内部和矩阵报告
enables you basically to plug in any
使您基本上可以插入任何
type of monitoring system that you want
您想要的监控系统类型
and basically collect so every time
基本上每次都收集
there is an update on some metric
有一些指标的更新
understand that there's those metrics
了解有那些指标
and now are being taken
现在正在被带走
the client-side right we're not talking
客户端的权利，我们不是在说
about the broker we're talking about the
关于我们正在谈论的经纪人
applications and every time your clients
应用程序以及您的客户每次
they have an update on a metric they
他们更新了指标
basically this this method is triggered
基本上这个方法被触发
it's a callback and you received
这是一个回调，您收到了
actually Kafka metric without the data
实际上没有数据的卡夫卡指标
you need and basically we got we got
您需要，基本上我们得到了
that value and we publish to be shown on
该值，我们发布以显示在
that port that I just showed to you but
我刚刚向您显示的那个端口，但是
there's more than that monitoring is a
监控不仅仅是一个
cross-cutting concern you don't want
您不想要的跨领域关注点
that logic to be to be polluting your
这种逻辑会污染你的
business code business code is really
商业代码商业代码真的是
important in banking we cannot make many
在银行业务中很重要，我们不能赚很多
mistakes there so we want really clean
那里的错误，所以我们想要真正的干净
code on that area and tough guy also
该区域的代码，硬汉也
facilitates that a Kafka has a has a
有助于卡夫卡有一个
concept that is very familiar for you
您很熟悉的概念
all for sure but I don't see people
一切肯定，但我看不到人
talking a lot about it about it but you
谈论很多关于它，但是你
can use I think I lost one of my
可以使用，我想我失去了我的一个
bookmarks oh yeah this one so it's an
书签哦，是的，这是一个
interceptor so Kafka also also allows
拦截器，所以卡夫卡还允许
you to hook in interceptors on the topic
您可以挂接有关该主题的拦截器
so you can say every every producer will
所以你可以说每个制作人都会
be an interceptor and you can basically
成为拦截者，您基本上可以
use that interceptor to to get the data
使用该拦截器获取数据
you need and get the metric from it so
您需要并从中获取指标，因此
you can really take it completely a part
您真的可以完全参与其中
of your business code so whenever there
您的业​​务代码，因此无论何时何地
is a there is a new message sent to a
有一个新消息发送到
topic it will be an interceptor and you
主题将是一个拦截器，你
can also do that for for consumers for
也可以为消费者做到这一点
producers and for streams and when I
生产者和流，当我
talk about streams important to notion
谈论对概念重要的流
in Kafka that you need it's important to
在卡夫卡，您需要
understand when you talk about streams
了解您谈论流时
streams are a high-level abstraction
流是高级抽象
well around the consumer and a producer
在消费者和生产者周围
so everything you can do for consumer or
因此，您可以为消费者或
for producer you can basically do with a
对于生产者，您基本上可以使用
stream as well and basically what Kafka
流以及基本上什么卡夫卡
does behind the scenes when you create a
当您创建一个
stream it creates a consumer an equator
流产生消费者赤道
produce it for you so it's also
为你生产，所以它也是
important to remember that like if you
重要的是要记住，就像你
set one thread for a calf the stream
为小牛设置一个线程
basically behind the scenes it will
基本上在幕后
create at least tweet words usually for
通常至少创建推文单词
because it creates one thread for the
因为它为
consumer one thread for the processor
消费者一个处理器线程
won't wait for the producer to push to a
不会等到制片人推到
buffer and another to add to actually
缓冲区和另一个要添加到实际
dispatch that that information
发送该信息
work so this is the matrix part it
工作，所以这是矩阵部分
really makes it very simple everything
真的让一切变得非常简单
we can get from Kafka and I'm gonna show
我们可以从卡夫卡那里得到，我要证明
show you know a little bit about how we
告诉你一些关于我们如何
do that first match just to make it to
做第一场比赛只是为了
make it more explicit and we wanna see
使它更明确，我们想看看
some code from that as well
也有一些代码
yeah but I think this is back now I
是的，但我想现在又回来了
don't know how it happened it magically
不知道这是怎么发生的
happened okay
好吧
let's tell you a bit about Kafka streams
让我们告诉您一些有关Kafka流的信息
and join so the first concept here that
并加入这里的第一个概念
it's interesting is the yeah we have a
有趣的是，我们有一个
broker and the first thing here that
经纪人，这里的第一件事
takes apart
分解
what Kafka streams does compared to
卡夫卡流与之相比
spark or flink is that Kafka streams
火花或闪烁是卡夫卡流
running your own application that's what
运行自己的应用程序
I mentioned a little bit in the
我提到了一点
beginning it's not running in external
开始它不在外部运行
manage broker and using external workers
管理经纪人并使用外部工人
it's actually running inside your spring
它实际上在你的 Spring 里运行
boot application that's why you have so
引导应用程序就是为什么
much control over it
对其有很多控制
to scale down scale etc so think about
缩小比例等，所以考虑
this like a sprint boot application and
这就像冲刺启动应用程序，
now we have a topic that's the initial
现在我们有一个最初的话题
topic remember in the first step we get
第一步要记住的话题
the topic from the market we push to the
市场上的主题我们推向
initial topic and there's a second
最初的话题，还有第二个
concept here which is extremely
这里的概念非常
important is the duality between the log
重要的是日志之间的对偶
when Kafka because every entry in the
当卡夫卡，因为在每个条目
log in Kafka have a key and that key
登录卡夫卡有一个钥匙，那个钥匙
brings you like it's you can think of
带给您喜欢的感觉
like a primary key in the database you
就像数据库中的主键一样
can use that key to do joins so when you
可以使用该键进行联接，因此当您
think about every entry that goes to the
考虑一下进入
log in Kafka it has a key and you can
登录卡夫卡，它有一个钥匙，你可以
think of it like a primary key just to
认为它只是主键
make it easy everyone understands the
让每个人都容易理解
concept of a primary key right and then
主键权利的概念，然后
we have the raw tick then we have the
我们有原始的刻度线，然后我们有
second topic this is where our business
第二个话题，这是我们的业务
intelligence is so the data we need to
情报就是我们需要的数据
make this information that we get here
使这些信息我们到达这里
useful for our internal applications
对我们的内部应用有用
it's in a separate topic and we use a
它在一个单独的主题中，我们使用
concept called a globe okay table I will
我将称为地球仪好的表的概念
use the globe okay table the globe okay
使用地球仪还可以表地球仪还可以
table give you many things for free
桌子免费提供许多东西
first of all it saves automatically for
首先，它会自动保存为
you the last update in any key that you
您在任何键中的最新更新
push to that topic so if there's any p
推送到该主题，因此如果有任何问题
date from an external system to this
从外部系统到此日期
topic let's say or business analysts
可以说话题还是业务分析师
they they now remove a specific tick
他们现在删除特定的刻度
that we don't trade anymore so we cannot
我们不再交易了，所以我们不能
trade or there is a new type of
交易或有一种新的
instrument that we want to trade when
我们想要交易的工具
this goes to this topic it automatically
这将自动转到该主题
saves for you so it think of it and a
为您省钱，让它想到了
look look this is running in your local
看，这在您本地运行
application which is great here because
这里的应用很棒
basically you can use this like
基本上你可以像这样使用
a cache but it's much simpler than a
缓存，但是比缓存简单得多
cache now you don't have to manage any
现在缓存，您无需管理任何
more like when you have to put or delete
更像是您必须放置或删除时
from the cache you get all these for
从缓存中获取所有这些信息
free and what Kafka does it materializes
免费，卡夫卡实现了什么
that in a rocks DB instance by the fool
在笨蛋的岩石数据库实例中
you can also use the different key value
您还可以使用其他键值
store here if you want but that's the
如果您想在这里存储，那就是
default one extremely performant for
默认一名表现出色的
SSDs so another point to keep in mind
SSD，因此要记住的另一点
run in SSD environments and now you can
在SSD环境中运行，现在您可以
basically do a join here so the flow
基本上在这里加入，所以流程
here is constant this is a case stream
这是恒定的，这是一个案例流
so this never stops there is a new stock
所以这永远不会停止
exchange opening there is never stop
交流开放永无止境
just 24/7 this data it's a bit more
这个数据只有24/7，还有更多
static but can also be updated as you
静态的，但也可以在您更新时更新
will the performance here would be great
这里的表演会很棒吗
even if you have many updates in the
即使您有很多更新
inside but in our case it doesn't and
里面，但在我们的情况下，它不
what you do it's a simple join like we
您要做的就是像我们这样的简单加入
all see and finally when we do the join
大家看到了，最后当我们加入时
between these values we push to a topic
在这些值之间，我们推动一个主题
where now this information makes sense
现在这些信息有意义
for our internal systems and from there
从内部系统开始
we continue and remember how this it's
我们继续并记住这是怎么回事
flowing here thousands per second it's
每秒流向这里数千
joining and now this is taking 100
加入，现在需要100
milliseconds so all the time and that's
毫秒，所以一直如此
that's one of the benefits of it but
那是它的好处之一，但是
please keep in mind this side and this
请记住这一点，这
side because I'm going to show you the
一边，因为我要告诉你
code that does that and that's another
做到这一点的代码，那是另一个
part that's quite interesting because
这部分很有趣，因为
it's it's quite simplified by Khafre
这是Khafre相当简化的
yeah so can you I don't know if it's oh
是的，你能不知道是不是
yeah and the show good Thanks
是的，表演很好，谢谢
we're almost there okay yeah so I'm
我们快到了，是的，所以我
gonna show you that there's some
会告诉你有一些
configuration around it I probably saw
我大概看到的配置
the talk yesterday about Kafka you can
昨天关于卡夫卡的谈话你可以
do configuration around it and then
围绕它进行配置，然后
basically I'm going to show what's
基本上我要展示什么
really important here it's the focus on
非常重要，这是重点
what we're doing first of all of course
我们首先要做的是
because you worst your deserializing the
因为您最糟糕的是反序列化
information from one topic and and
来自一个主题的信息，以及
serializing to another topic basically
基本上序列化到另一个主题
deserializing is realizing then you have
反序列化就是实现
a service say realizer deserialized
反序列化服务的实现者
that's the name Saudi and then you have
那是沙特的名字，然后你有
an Avro type this is a novel schema
Avro类型，这是一种新颖的模式
average schemas give you a lot of
平均模式给您很多
advantages we're going to comment a
我们将要评论的优势
little bit more about this later and
稍后再讲一点
then this is your bailiwick a table what
那这是你的百利威克桌子吗
this does it's it's reading for that
这是它的阅读
specific topic and is basically
具体主题，基本上是
materializing it to locally in your
在您的本地实现它
application with the specific e image
带有特定电子图像的应用程序
specific Avro type and this is all you
特定的Avro类型，这就是您的全部
need to do to have your cash if you
需要做的是拥有现金，如果您
there's an update on that topic you can
您可以在该主题上进行更新
just send a key with a new and it's
只需发送一个新的密钥，
deleted for you if there is a new value
如果有新值，则为您删除
it's automatically automatically add to
它会自动自动添加到
you to that to that local cash and this
您到那个当地现金和这个
is running locally and when I mean
在本地运行，当我的意思是
running locally because this is
在本地运行，因为这是
extremely important for us as well I get
对我们来说也非常重要
on this key value store takes
在此键值存储上
nanoseconds in a server less than 0
小于0的服务器中的纳秒
milliseconds that are experienced on
经历的毫秒数
that it's extremely fast it's locally
它在本地非常快
the rocks DB also has local cache so in
岩石数据库也有本地缓存​​，因此
the end is everything running in your
最终一切都在您的体内运行
local application it's extremely
本地应用程序非常
efficient and then we do a cockade
有效率，然后我们做一个帽徽
stream from the auto topic that's the
从自动主题流
continuous flow of sticks and that's
持续不断的流动，那就是
what you need to do these two lines and
您需要执行这两行操作以及
then you do a join and now you do a join
然后您进行加入，现在您进行加入
and you say by symbol and you do that
然后用符号说，然后
joint and once you do that join if there
联合，一旦完成，如果存在
is something it will basically sync to
它基本上会同步到
the next topic and then you do two and
下一个主题，然后您做两个，然后
this sends to the new topic and on top
这将发送到新主题并在顶部
of that what's quite interesting here is
其中非常有趣的是
that our applications they also need
他们还需要我们的应用程序
that metadata that's generated by our by
由我们生成的元数据
our business people to be used in
我们的业务人员
different parts of the front-end and etc
前端的不同部分等
and you can actually add basically
实际上，您可以基本上添加
it's I need to scrub it basically you
我基本上需要擦洗你
can on top of that globe okay table you
可以在那个地球仪上面吗
can do expose those values as a key
可以将这些值作为键公开
value store in two lines of code so now
值存储在两行代码中，所以现在
you have here how the metadata that you
你在这里有如何元数据
need the join the enrichment of the
需要加入的丰富
message and you can actually expose out
消息，您实际上可以暴露出来
the data we do the same for the price by
我们对价格所做的数据相同
the way so when you go to the
这样的方式，当你去
application and you see the stock price
应用程序，您会看到股票价格
we're doing basically the same or expose
我们在做基本相同或暴露
we expose the price from a K table and
我们从K表中公开价格
this is extremely performant as well
这也是非常出色的
from there we go back to the
从那里我们回到
presentation and team is going to let's
演示文稿和团队将让我们
go over this team is going to talk about
越过这个团队要谈论
a little bit about our local local
关于我们当地人的一点
development set up yeah so you saw
开发设置是的，所以你看到了
already some quite advanced topics that
已经有一些相当高级的话题
Marcus showed us maybe you got inspired
马库斯向我们展示了也许您受到启发
by just long yesterday and and Victor
直到昨天和维克多
from confluence they are really great in
从汇合来看，他们真的很棒
creating hello world scalable
创建可扩展的Hello World
applications with all respect I really
我非常尊重所有应用程序
like those talks but you probably go
像那些谈话，但你可能去
back work to work on on Monday so maybe
回到星期一工作，也许
you got expired so we're if you would
你已经过期了，所以我们是
like to use this stuff where do you
喜欢在哪里使用这个东西
start right so because we were also a
从正确开始，因为我们也是
bit struggling let's say if we go back
有点挣扎，如果我们回去
three years ago so so we started out
三年前，所以我们开始了
with with widower two to run everything
与with夫二运行一切
locally because of course we have a
在本地，因为我们当然有一个
Kafka cluster on test environments on
Kafka集群在测试环境上
different fireman's but yeah if Marcus
不同的消防员，但如果是马库斯，
is going to create or publish a lot of
将要创建或发布很多
data or the topic I might also consume
数据或我可能还会使用的主题
that data and and yeah we stepped on
数据，是的，我们继续
each other's thoughts quite quickly so
彼此的想法很快
we decided to to isolate our
我们决定隔离我们
environments run everything locally we
环境在本地运行一切
initially started with with creating our
最初是从创建我们的
own dr. Kafka images and along the way
自己的博士卡夫卡图片和一路走来
confluence the company behind Kafka
融合卡夫卡背后的公司
nowadays provides you with knives docker
如今为您提供了刀码头工
images also for shooty per Kafka manager
每位Kafka经理也对图片进行拍摄
and
和
we adore Christ our own applications as
我们崇拜基督我们自己的申请
I mentioned this custom producer is
我提到这个定制制作人是
quite important for us and and this
对我们来说非常重要
whole project grow into a lab project
整个项目成长为实验室项目
which we basically use every day in our
我们基本上每天都在使用
work to try out new stuff we can break
尝试新的东西，我们可以打破
everything and and and yeah the things
一切，而且是的
we learn there we bring it back to the
我们在那里学习，将其带回
to the real project within 9 G and it's
到9 G以内的真实项目，
also a really nice experience for us to
对我们来说也是一个非常好的经历
to learn more about the latest and
以了解更多有关最新和
greatest in spring Bhutan Kafka let's go
Spring 最伟大的不丹卡夫卡去吧
to some code to IntelliJ yeah so
到IntelliJ的一些代码
hopefully you're all using a spring boot
希望你们都在使用 spring boot
then it's really easy to get started
那真的很容易上手
with with spring Kafka you just drop in
随着 Spring 的卡夫卡，你只是在
the spring Kafka dependency let me show
Spring 的卡夫卡依赖性让我展示
up you're still running right guys yeah
你仍然在跑对的家伙
so it's it's a bit hot here it's fine
所以这里有点热
okay let's okay so let's make it a
好吧，好吧，所以让它成为
little bit bigger so this is an example
稍大一点，所以这是一个例子
of our of our dopost file so confluent
我们的dopost文件如此融合
provides us with its nose nice docker
为我们提供了一个不错的码头工人
images there's a lot of a lot of
图像有很多
configuration around it but but yeah you
周围的配置，但对，你
will learn along the way how to do this
将沿途学习如何做到这一点
we use a skimmer NSC and fr skimmers are
我们使用撇渣器NSC，fr撇渣器是
basically the contract with between the
基本上与
consumer and the producer and they are
消费者和生产者，他们是
stored in this this registry we run a
存储在此注册表中，我们运行
kafka manager that's the UI on top of it
kafka管理器，这是它之上的UI
to see what's going on we use Postgres
看看发生了什么，我们使用Postgres
for the database and we have to dr. Rast
对于数据库，我们必须博士。 ast
applications here so that's how we
这里的应用程序，这就是我们
basically start yeah working locally
基本上是开始在当地工作
most of the time we focus on one
大多数时候我们专注于
application running in IntelliJ where
在IntelliJ中运行的应用程序
we're working in and the rest is
我们正在工作，其余的是
basically running in the background for
基本上在后台运行
us that works works pretty well okay
我们工作正常，很好
yeah that may be a quick introduction in
是的，这可能是快速入门
in F Rho you need those dependencies
在F Rho中，您需要那些依赖项
to create yeah basically Java objects
基本上是创建Java对象
out of the afro schemas you can also use
在非洲模式之外，您还可以使用
plain JSON or we started out with
纯JSON或我们从
problem protobuf indeed better way yeah
问题protobuf确实是更好的方法
it's really great to use effort there
在那里努力真的很棒
because it enforces the contract between
因为它强制执行
the consumer and the producer so let's
消费者和生产者，所以让我们
show you an actual Afro schema so this
显示一个实际的非洲模式
is one of our events this is an event
这是我们的活动之一
when a customer deletes one of his
当客户删除他的一个
alerts from the UI and then we send this
用户界面发出警报，然后我们发送此警报
alert out of a tool to the Kafka topic
从工具中警惕Kafka主题
and this is basically definition it's
这基本上是定义
it's probably the most simple ever
这可能是有史以来最简单的
schema we have here so we have the
我们在这里有架构，所以我们有
unique identifier of the alert the
警报的唯一标识符
identifier of the customer and the
客户的标识符和
symbol that uniquely identifies the
唯一标识
stock with this Kafka arrow plug-in
该Kafka箭头插件的库存
basically for formation and it will
基本上是为了形成，它将
automatically create a Java object out
自动创建一个Java对象
of it maybe you saw the talk yesterday
也许你昨天看了演讲
so don't look at that code it's not
所以不要看那个代码，不是
really nice to read but it works pretty
真的很不错，但是效果很好
fine we just use this to to push the
很好，我们只是用它来推动
data on Kafka yeah then you of course
关于Kafka的数据，那么您当然可以
would like to to produce some data on
想产生一些数据
the topic right so let's let's take a
正确的话题，让我们来
look how we actually going to produce
看看我们实际上将如何生产
data to to Kafka you are pretty sure
数据肯定到Kafka
familiar with all kinds of templates
熟悉各种模板
right JDBC template rest template and of
正确的JDBC模板其余模板和
course in the spring model we also have
当然在 Spring 模型中我们也有
a Kafka template here to produce to the
一个Kafka模板，可以生成
topic and that's basically yeah what you
话题，基本上就是你
need to do to send data to a topic so
需要发送数据到一个主题，所以
it's in this case let's focus on the on
在这种情况下，让我们专注于
the alert the leader defend so this is
领导者警惕的警戒是
the
的
we generated code rights for afro and we
我们为非洲产生了代码权利，我们
basically say a template sent this event
基本上说模板发送了此事件
to a certain topic and here's the data
某个主题，这是数据
that's probably all you all you need in
那可能就是您所需要的全部
the talk yesterday by just long he
昨天的谈话他说了很久
created a lot of stuff in Java
用Java创建了很多东西
configuration nowadays you can also
如今，您还可以配置
really nicely configure everything in
真的很好地配置了所有内容
your application lots of properties or
您的应用程序具有很多特性或
your general depends on what you what
你的将军取决于你什么
you like but this is basically the
你喜欢，但这基本上是
Congress you say here is my Kafka brocco
国会，你说这是我的卡夫卡·布罗科
runner running you can have one or
跑步者可以拥有一个或
multiple depending on your situation
倍数取决于您的情况
this is the serializer for the key and
这是密钥的序列化器，
this is the serializer for ephraim this
这是ephraim的序列化器
then we point our schema registry and
然后我们指向架构注册表
this is something we need for them for
这是我们需要他们的东西
the metrics that Marcus just showed so
Marcus刚刚显示的指标
this is the producer side of things and
这是事物的生产者方面，
yeah sprinkle curve will create under
是的，洒水曲线会在
the hood a Kafka producer because that's
罩卡夫卡制片人，因为那是
what you need to basically produce this
您基本上需要产生什么
data to to the topic on the other end
数据到另一端的主题
you would like to consume the data in
您想使用其中的数据
this example we directly also consume
这个例子我们也直接消耗
the data in a consumer so this is the
消费者中的数据，所以这是
other way around it's pretty pretty
相反，它很漂亮
straightforward yeah so let's look at a
是的，所以让我们来看一个
really really simple consumer this is an
真的很简单的消费者，这是一个
example where we consume a alert deleted
删除警报的示例
offense you have a Kafka listener and
进攻你有一个卡夫卡听众，
yeah that will basically deliver this
是的，基本上可以做到这一点
event to to this method you can even do
您甚至可以对此方法进行操作
a validation on incoming data right so
对传入数据进行验证，这样
that's not really specific to spring
那不是 Spring 特有的
Kafka but it just leverages yeah the the
卡夫卡，但它只是利用了
good things that that spring is pretty
那 Spring 很漂亮的好东西
good a versus and in this case we just
很好的对抗，在这种情况下，我们只是
call the meta registry from micrometre
从微米调用元注册表
but this is a really simple example you
但这是一个非常简单的例子
can of course call yeah and a downstream
当然可以叫耶和下游
surface or whatever you would like to do
表面或您想做的任何事情
but this is basically a simple
但这基本上很简单
producer/consumer example
生产者/消费者示例
yeah I think that's that that's yeah
是的，我认为那就是那样
let's use the three final minutes to
我们用最后三分钟来
talk a little bit about lessons learned
谈论一些经验教训
and share a few of the drawbacks and
并分享一些缺点
what we learned is I think this is quite
我们学到的是，我认为这很
important so a little bit first of all
重要的是首先
before using spring Kafka we recommend
在使用 Spring 卡夫卡之前，我们建议
that you understand basically Kafka
你基本上了解卡夫卡
behind it there's a lot to it it's
它背后有很多东西
distributed computing there are the
分布式计算有
complexities there you need to know how
那里的复杂性你需要知道如何
to configure how to scale is not only
配置如何缩放不仅
about adding nodes you need to have the
关于添加节点，您需要
proper partitioning so this is quite
适当的分区，所以这是相当
interesting quite important
有趣的很重要
Avro it's really life saving basically
Avro基本上可以拯救生命
Avro enforces a contract between the
Avro在
producer in the consumer and basically
消费者中的生产者，基本上
you cannot push a message that's invalid
您不能推送无效的消息
to the to the topic it really helps from
到该主题确实有帮助
the business perspective can still be
业务角度仍然可以
invalid of course it can be it can have
当然无效，可以是
a wrong value but the serialization in
一个错误的值，但是序列化在
this realization process is enforced and
这个实现过程被强制执行，
it's guaranteed because then the message
这是有保证的，因为这样消息
will always be able impossible to
将永远不可能
serialize this realize it simple it's
序列化，这很简单
important to think a little bit about
考虑一点很重要
partitions before you start basically
开始之前先分区
because if you have to think if you do
因为如果您必须考虑是否
joins the the topics you are doing joins
加入您正在做的主题
they should have the same number of
他们应该有相同数量的
partitions with some exceptions if
分区，如果有一些例外
basically if you're using global K table
基本上，如果您使用全局K表
like was the case because everything
之所以如此，是因为一切
goes running on the side client on the
在客户端上运行
client side this can be a bit different
客户端这可能会有所不同
but if we're doing for instance a normal
但是如果我们正在做一个正常的
cake table and you want to horizonte
蛋糕桌，你想
upscale then you really need the same
高档，那么您真的需要相同的
number of partitions between the topics
主题之间的分区数
and this is one of the key important and
这是重要的关键之一，
also if you want to scale Kafka our fort
如果您想扩展我们的堡垒卡夫卡
is possible it can be hard to do without
没有它可能很难做到
downtime and in our case we don't have
停机时间，在我们的情况下，我们没有
that privilege to have this downtime so
有这种停机时间的特权
that's something important for us
这对我们很重要
monitoring is extremely important we use
监控非常重要，我们使用
micrometer we're really happy with it
千分尺我们真的很满意
simple easy to use very very easy to
简单易用非常非常容易
sync the data to elastic search maybe if
将数据同步到弹性搜索，如果
you have or primitives it will adapt to
您拥有或将适应的原语
many different types of systems that you
您可以使用许多不同类型的系统
need a little bit about we really like
需要一点关于我们真的很喜欢
how the Khafre clients are backwards
Khafre客户如何落后
compatible so when whenever
兼容，因此无论何时何地
they deliver a new version of the client
他们提供了新版本的客户端
usually you can just upgrade the client
通常你可以升级客户端
without waiting for the broker and this
不用等待经纪人和这个
is amazing as a developer is something
作为一名开发人员是一件很棒的事
who really loved it because we always
谁真的喜欢它，因为我们总是
want to to be taking advantage of the
想要利用
latest features and crafting general is
最新功能和手工艺一般是
backwards compatible between clients
客户端之间向后兼容
Kafka stream skate table globe ok tables
卡夫卡流滑板桌地球仪确定表
integrative queries that I talked about
我谈到的综合查询
this a little bit with you it's
这一点与你是
important to understand the difference
了解差异很重要
between them a globe ok table if you
他们之间的地球仪确定表，如果你
need a lot of scale can be tricky
需要很多规模可能会很棘手
because basically about a table is going
因为基本上是一张桌子
to consume from all the topics available
从所有可用主题中消费
for that specific for the other
对于其他的
partition sorry and describe is really
分区抱歉，并描述是真的
your friend when you are doing streaming
进行流媒体播放时与您的朋友
I have a few seconds let's finish this
我有几秒钟让我们完成这个
streaming kafka streams gives you
流卡夫卡流给你
exactly ones guarantee by configuration
完全由配置保证
which is amazing if you know distributed
如果您知道分布式的，那就太了不起了
computing you know it's one of the
计算，你知道这是其中之一
hardest things to do and in kafka
在卡夫卡最难的事情
streams it's basically for granted it's
流基本上是理所当然的
just a configuration plan I had a
只是我有一个配置计划
topology try to make it small a
拓扑尝试使其变小
topologies that a set of joints that you
一组关节的拓扑结构
do between topics because we had that's
在主题之间做，因为我们有
a single deployable unit so if you want
一个可部署单元，因此如果您愿意
to scale independently it's important
独立扩展很重要
that you plan ahead this topology and
您预先计划此拓扑，并且
yeah that's it
是的就是这样
thank you very much for being here
非常感谢你在这里
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]